joji_antony@gmx.com +91 96323 41954

Profile

Back end leaning full stack software engineer with 5+ years of professional experience building IT infrastructure software. Proficient in developing beautiful software systems that have very high requirements of stability, security and scale. Deeply committed to usability, maintainability and security. Loves shipping, helping businesses and customers succeed.

Education

Undergraduate College Education

College of Engineering, Trivandrum

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering

Technologies

Programming Languages

Python, C, C++, Java, Javascript, Perl ...

Frameworks

Python Flask, Python Django, JavaScript Dojo, ReactJS, Java EE 6 ...

Tools

Docker, Postgres, MySQL, UNIX, Jboss, Git, Subversion, Maven, GNU Toolchain ...

Platforms

Heroku, AWS, Linux

Work Experience and Projects

Work Experience Employed by Nutanix since June 2016

Nutanix Application Mobility Fabric Team

2016 - present

Accomplishments

Implemented error handling for AMF Xplorer

Implemented infinite scrolling back end support for AMF Xplorer

HPE Hyperconverged cloud

2016 - 2016

Front end developer at HPE Hyperconverged cloud team

Accomplishments

Implemented image management

Technologies

ReactJS, Webpack, Gulp, SASS

HP Network Management Center

2013 - 2016

Worked as a core developer and security engineer for HP's Network Management Software called Network Node Manager i

Also worked as lead developer and lab support engineer for NNMi Network Engineer's

Toolset

Accomplishments

- Improving SNMP v3 USM specification compliance in the SNMP stack
- Work on enabling Network Function Virtualization support
- Port the Network Engineer's Toolset to Linux; including build and test infrastructure
- Add support for Safari on Mac
- Adding CSRF protection to the NNMi

Technologies

Java EE, JavaScript Dojo framework, Java Swing, etc

HP Network Node Manager 7.x lab support

2011 - 2013

Lab support engineer for Hewlett-Packard's premier Network Management Solution called NNM

Accomplishments

- Adding support for filtering in the Applet based UI
- Solved many multi-threading issues that were frustrating customers
- Solved many cache coherence issues

Technologies

C, C++, Perl, SQL, Java

Side projects

Plivo Call Center

2015-Present

Functional call center application using Plivo API running on the Heroku Platform https://github.com/simula67/plivo-callcenter

Open source work Perl 6 LWP

Merged a patch to Perl 6 LWP to match output of Perl 5 LWP https://github.com/simula67/perl6-lwp-simple

Perl 6 Test Suite

Merged a patch to refactor some of Perl 6 official test suite https://github.com/simula67/roast

Snaplr packaging for Chocolatey

Packaging Snaplr for chocolatey https://github.com/simula67/chocolateytemplates

Online Profiles

Blog: https://simula67.wordpress.com about.me: https://about.me/jojiantony